Wait. In The Hitchhikers Guide
to the Galaxy...
...isn't 43 the answer to the question of life,
the universe, and everything?
That's 42, dumb-ass.
(Raj:)Hey, hey.
(Raj:)Feelings.
(Howard:)We should stop. I'm exhausted.
(Raj:)Yeah, me too.
We've got more important things to do.
Who cares what stupid 43 means?
- Not me.
- Let's go home.
(Raj:)- Want to get something to eat?
- Sounds good.
- What the balls is 43?
- I have to know.
(Howard:)Hi.
(Penny:)Hey. Shouldn't you be out with your gang...
...spray-painting equations
on the side of buildings?
- Come on, I'm sorry.
- I just can't believe you don't trust me.
No, I do. Of course I do.
(Penny:)Then why did you embarrass me in front of
my friend? Who knew exactly who you were.
- Really?
- Your picture's on my refrigerator.